[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
Don't!
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Why did you shoot him?!
Django! That wasn't part
of our deal!
We're not going to kill him.
We're just going to scare him.
You betrayed me!
I'll never forget
what you did to me.
If I see you here again,
I will kill you!
I'll serve my sentence here.
I didn't do anything wrong,
that I was falsely accused.
We'll have one less
troublemaker in here.
You're free to go.
This is a hold up!
Gabo!
Your crew with Django
is ruthless.
You'll even go after cold rice.
I need backup on Joaquin Street!
There's a holdup happening
on a bus!
This is the police! Stop!
I'm not the robber!
I'm the one who helped them!
Damn you, Gabo!
He's not the robber!
He helped us!
Poor thing! Help him!
You pervert!
You took advantage of me!
Took advantage?
You're the one who kissed me!
You took advantage of me!
You think you're all that, huh?
You're beautiful.
- What's your name?
- You're unbelievable.
You really had the guts
to ask my name.
[MAX] Sam!
Look, I'm leaving.
Take care of the robbers.
- [MAX] Sam! Sam!
- Hey!
- Hold on! We're not done!
- [MAX] Are you alright?
- [SAM] Yes. I'm fine.
- Miss! You guys look cute.
How fortunate.
You truly are my lucky charm.
[SMACK]
- They tried to rob us!
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
No one got hurt,
except for the bad guys.
[POLICE] Step aside! Step aside!
Are you alright?
- Huh?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- [MAX] Are you sure?
- [SAM] Thanks for arriving.
[MAX] Luckily you called
right away!
Men! Secure the perimeter!
Handcuff all suspects.
Make sure of that.
Put them in the patrol car!
- No one escapes, okay?
- Max! Max! Max!
What happened here?
NLEA got a call that
a robbery was happening.
We responded right away,
but when we arrived,
the real hero, NCIA agent
Samantha Jacinto--
She quickly took action,
and caught the robbers.
Estrella!
Here with us today
is the hero
who stopped the robbery
in the bus,
NCIA agent Sam Jacinto.
What happened here, and how
did you stop the robbery?
I was driving earlier
when I noticed the bus.
The driver
was driving recklessly,
so they might get
into an accident.
I approached it,
and saw it was a mess inside.
Apparently, there was a robbery.
The robber took a shot at me,
so I just did the same.
I cuffed them here,
but there was a man who helped.
He's the one
who protected the passengers.
Where is he?
Can we interview him?
- He left.
- Oli, Oli!
Let's look for details
on the bus
and from the passengers,
come on.
- Thank you, thank you.
- [MAX] Okay.
Sure that's clear?
Sam?
Who's that man
you were talking to?
No one. Don't mind him.
I'm going back to the office,
they're probably looking for me.
Be careful, okay?
- Thank you.
- You know how mommy is.
Alright, I'll take care of this.
Estrella, make sure
everyone's safe.
[ESTRELLA] Yes, ma'am.
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
[TOWN CRIER] Calling
all neighbors!
This is our chance!
It is time for us
to take action!
Stop idling around!
And you!
Stop giving them money!
How will we earn their respect?
Nothing good comes from gossip.
Mind your own business
and work on yourselves!
Stop relying on luck!
Success won't just fall
into your lap.
What else are you
waiting for, neighbors?
Let's take action!
I'm back
where I belong!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTERING]
How's it going?
Hey!
[WOMAN 1] Pedring,
you're out here drinking again!
You useless bastard!
I'll drag you back
to your mother!
[WOMAN 2] Come and buy one!
Come and buy one!
Come and get pagpag
(scavenged leftovers)!
Pagpag (scavenged leftovers)!
Come get it here!
- Miss!
- Come buy here!
- My favorite! How much is this?
- One hundred.
This used to be thirty!
Why did the price go up?
[WOMAN 2] Prices have
increased since the war.
- [WOMAN 2] Thank you.
- No problem.
Hmm. [SMOOCHES]
My favorite! [CHUCKLES]
[WOMAN 2] Come and get yours!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
Our girl just scored a point!
Just like the person next to me,
- she scored big!
- C'mon, girl!
[CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
They'll lose! That's nothing!
[INAUDIBLE]
[CROWD CHEERING]
Team Emeruit is leading!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Gosh!
- Team Emeruit--
- It's Gabo!
It's Gabo!
[WOMAN 1] Gabo!
Your hair is so long!
You're here!
Gabo!
[WOMAN 2] Look, it's Gabo!
- Look, it's Gabo!
- Tekla!
- Tekla! Tekla!
- [CROWD SCREAMING]
Where's my grandchild?!
What's going on?
- Gabo is out!
- It's Gabo!
[SCREAMING]
[SQUEALING] Gabo! Gabo!
Step aside! Gabo!
[SQUEALING] Gabo!
[CROWD CHEEERING]
[SMOOCHING]
Gabo, I've missed you!
Why didn't you
tell me you were going home?
Tekla?
Yes, it's me!
- [MAN] Hey!
- Ouch! Hey, it hurts!
Hey, what's going on?
Step aside!
He doesn't like you
because you're all ugly!
They're attacking
my granddaughter!
Nobody is interested
in people like you!
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- Hey! Stop that!
- You're ugly! Ugly!
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
That's enough! Enough!
[TEKLA] C'mon,
I'll bring you back to my place!
I mean... back to your place.
[IBYANG] What's this?
Why did you only make this much?
We can't afford to slow down,
or we'll lose our customers!
What's going on here!
Hurry up!
Wash those properly!
You can start using this.
Don't fill it up too much,
I'll lose money!
Seal it properly
so it looks legit.
Start moving!
Hey, you..
Make sure to charge extra
on the buses you ride, okay?
Go, hurry!
[MAN] I'll teach you, okay?
Do you see this gun?
This isn't a toy,
this is a deadly weapon!
Do you understand?
- [CHILDREN] Yes, sir!
- Alright, run along!
Yes, sir!
Where's the boss?
He's right there.
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, why are you here?
- What's wrong?
- We need some money.
Come on.
[CURIOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[IBYANG] Django!
What is it?
These kids are looking for you.
[IBYANG] Marites,
why don't you come with me?
Clean up there, too.
Boss, here's all
the money we made.
- Pa.
- Hmm?
What's going on?
Oh.
Would you look at that!
You've already hit
your quota in just one week!
- For real?
- These kids of yours
are just built different!
Of course!
They can get out right away
since they're still kids, eh?
So just keep at it! [SMACKS]
Obviously. And don't lump us in
with Topak. That flop.
Why? What happened with Topak?
Cops caught them.
What now, Pops? Topak rakes in
quite a good amount, too.
Just let him stay there for now.
Take a short vacation inside.
Once the weather cools down,
then we'll get them out.
Hmm.
Right, then. Go and grab a bite,
boys.
- Hey.
- What?
[IBYANG] We struck it big, eh?
[INAUDIBLE]
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[HANDBRAKE CLICKS]
[THUDS]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[AVELINO] At least 30 bus
passengers made it safe
from a robbery by a group of men
at Joaquin Street in Manila.
Agent Samantha Jacinto
of the National Criminal
Investigation Agency or NCIA,
- saved the victims.
- Good morning, Ma'am Jacinto!
[SALVADOR] The hero who stopped
the robbery in the bus,
- NCIA Agent Sam Jacinto.
- Look at you go!
According to Jacinto,
she noticed the bus
running in a strange manner.
When she approached the vehicle,
she saw the criminals inside.
However, one man helped her
in fighting
- said criminals.
- Great job, ma'am!
Had you not been there
that group would've succeeded
again!
I just did what I had to do.
Wow!
- Wow, congrats!
- [ALL APPLAUDING]
We know it's your job,
Ma'am Jacinto.
But it still made us proud.
Good thing you beat them
even with just yourself!
Amazing! Badass!
Hey, watch your mouth!
What, you think Ma'am Sam
is incapable of doing so?
That's not it. We all know
we're very capable.
It just so happens
that it's Ma'am Jacinto's day.
Really? Spare me the flattery.
- Get back to your job.
- [LAUGHING]
- Amazing!
- Congrats!
- You were great!
- Congratulations!
Alright!
[AGENT 1] Ma'am, congrats!
[SAM] Thanks.
[AGENT 2] Good morning, ma'am!
- Ma'am, congrats!
- [AGENT 3] Congrats, ma'am!
Huh? What's this?
[KAREN] Wow!
- [FOLDER THUDS]
- Who sent this?
Why are you asking as if
you're not an investigator?
Sam.
How is it? Did you like it?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Mmm.
What's this for, sir?
I'm not sure.
What do you think?
Um...
It could be because...
I want to congratulate you
for saving those people.
Or it could also be because...
I'm still waiting for...
- you to say yes.
- [RALLOS] Oh!
My idol is truly
a smooth operator!
Ma'am Sam, can't you even say
a little thank you
for this sweet gesture?
Mm.
Thank you. Thank you, sir.
Excuse me.
[BOUQUET THUDS]
[CHAIR RATTLING]
- [CHAIR RATTLES]
- [THUDS]
[SEBASTIAN CLEARS THROAT]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Sam.
Is there something wrong?
Are you okay?
- Mm.
- [KAREN] Oh.
I know you like the back
of my hand.
There is.
It's not like you're allergic
to flowers.
[QUIRKY STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
There's just...
something that happened
during the incident.
What?!
What happened?!
There was...
a man who attempted to kiss me.
- [THUDS]
- That bastard!
Why did he kiss you?!
Is he one of the suspects?
A victim?
No.
I don't know why he's there
or even who-- who he is.
Who's that bastard?
Did you get his name?
Bring his ass to me!
I'll beat him up!
I won't spare him!
Wow. That random guy
beat you to it.
Exactly!
Can you all please stop
this nonsense?
You guys are so embarrassing,
you're too loud--
Sam, you don't deserve
to be disrespected like that!
Now, tell me who that man is!
Bring hiss ass to me! I'll beat
him up! I won't spare him!
I told you, enough!
I'm the one who got wronged
so I'm the one
who'll deal with it.
Once I find out who he is
I'll be the one to throw him
to jail and not you!
[SEBASTIAN SIGHS]
[KAREN] Oh, wow...
He's still courting her but he
already cares for her a lot.
Won't you just go out
with him already, ma'am?
I mean, you look good
together anyway.
[CASTOR] Team, let's go!
Sir Delgado is calling us.
- Let's go.
- Sam, come on.
[QUIRKY STIRRING MUSIC
CONTINUES]
[THUDS]
Jacinto.
[SAM] Sir.
Good job!
[DJANGO] You sure about this?
[MAN] We've been watching
them for days.
The owner leaves
at nine o'clock.
[DJANGO] How many stay behind?
[MAN] Two.
The wife and the maid.
Alright.
Wait until the man leaves.
We'll go in through the back.
Take everything.
It's all set, Django.
Alright, we're heading out.
[ROMY] Django!
This is Tuklaw.
He said he's got a job for us.
You guys handle that.
I'm heading out.
Right now?
- What's the job?
- We've got a hit.
A construction company owner
in Batangas.
The details are in the envelope.
How much?
Fifty thousand.
Half up front.
Once the job's done,
another fifty.
Full payment.
[CHUCKLES]
Damn it...
We've got a job in Camarin.
What are we supposed to do?
Django...
Your Uncle Romy and I
can handle this.
You sure, Pa? Can you manage?
[SCOFFS]
What do you take us for,
rookies?
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, Romy.
Get the guns ready.
It's always ready.
Always well-oiled so...
- [PAQUITO SCOFFS]
- [ROMY] Come on.
[MAN] Give me the ball!
Pass it!
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [KEYBOARD CLICKING]
- Hurry up!
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DABOY] A tough guy, huh?
[METAL SCREWING]
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Ma...
Ma, the water bill just arrived.
Pay it. It's only
two hundred pesos anyway.
Ma, it's not two hundred!
The bill is eight thousand!
What?
Why is it eight thousand?
Do we have a swimming pool
or something?
I don't know why
it's eight thousand...
- Kulas!
- What?
- Come look at this!
- Look, Pa.
It's eight thousand.
Yeah, it's eight thousand.
How could it possibly be
eight thousand?
Look over there!
Get the crowbar and the shovel.
- Hurry!
- Okay, Pa.
[DIDAY] Hurry up!
[ESTONG] Ma, move aside.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DIDAY] Go on, dig it up!
There could be a lot
of pipes connected to it!
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KULAS] Diday!
No wonder our bill's so high.
So many people are tapped
into our water line.
See? I told you.
You've all got some nerve!
Where's my machete?
[ESTONG] Ma!
Don't get too worked up!
Pa, stop her!
- Ma!
- [KULAS] Come on!
[ESTONG] Ma!
Ma!
- [DIDAY YELLING]
- [ESTONG] Ma!
Here comes Miss Diday again.
[DIDAY] You people are
unbelievable!
- Here comes another fight.
- [LAUGHS]
- You'll pay for this, okay?
- I got it!
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
[METAL SCREWING]
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [CHUCKLING]
- Wave it around!
Maybe you'll hit somebody!
- Hey, stop her!
- Go on, slash them!
- Run!
- Hey!
Rudy!
[WOMAN] Diday, you might
actually hit someone!
- What's going on?
- Diday's losing it again!
- I wonder why.
- Look at her!
How am I supposed to pay
eight thousand?
What's going on?
- What's Diday doing?
- Who knows?
She just suddenly went crazy.
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
Diday, you might hit someone
with that!
Hey, Diday!
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
- Hey!
- She's carrying a machete!
Stop that!
I barely recognized you, Tekla.
- You've really grown up.
- I'm even prettier now, right?
That's why those gays
are so jealous of me.
I was wondering who
they were arguing with.
[TEKLA CHUCKLES]
No wonder they're
so annoyed with you.
[OVERLAPPING CLAMOR]
What's going on?
[TEKLA] There.
Miss Diday's throwing a fit
again.
She probably found out that
everyone around here
is tapped into their water line.
Gabo?
Gabo!
- Gabo!
- Pa!
Pa!
- Gabo!
- Pa!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [DANTE] Gabo!
Gabo!
[GABO] Pa!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's Gabo! He's here!
- Oh!
- [DANTE] Gabo!
- Gabo!
- Aunty!
Thank God!
Tolits, Django needs
to know about this.
He won't last long here.
Django's going to come
after him right away.
- [CRYING] He's here.
- Hey.
- Gabo.
- Miss Betchay.
So you're finally home.
You didn't even tell us.
What should we do?
Come on!
Let's tell Django!
Let's go!
Nice entrance. You look like
you just got back from Saudi.
[LAUGHS]
Wow, Gabo!
- You've really changed.
- [DANTE] Yeah.
You look like a movie star.
[IPE] Gabo! Good thing
you're finally out.
We thought you'd be stuck
in there for a long time.
[BONG] What happened?
You bastard.
I thought you'd rot in there.
[MAMENG] Look at this guy!
Gabo, how'd you get out?
Were you released...
...or did you escape?
- Uh, Betchay.
- Yes?
Why don't you prepare some food?
- Yeah, we've got dried fish!
- Gabo must be starving.
- Come on, son.
- Come on, let's eat.
[GABO] Let's go.
Can you believe
he's already out?
[TEKLA] Let's eat!
- There, son.
- Sit over there.
- [TEKLA] Can I join?
- Sure.
[MAMENG] Come on in.
- Is it okay?
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
- Come on, let's eat.
Pa, I brought food too.
I bought it from the corner.
I've missed this.
- Pagpag?
- Yes!
It's been so long
since I've had it.
[BETCHAY] Give it to me.
I'll put it on a plate.
Really?
- Yeah.
- Up until now?
- That's still your favorite?
- Of course.
We all grew up eating that,
didn't we?
- Here you go.
- That's true.
I still remember how
we'd pick the pieces
- with the fewest bite marks.
- Right?
- Exactly.
- Go ahead, take some.
And it's from all kinds
of different restaurants.
That's why it's special!
- [LAUGHS]
- Mmm. Delicious!
[DELGADO] Please distribute.
The files I'm giving you now
contain your next case.
Large-scale illegal gold mining.
They're mining gold
and supplying it to
major jewelers in Chinatown.
We've also learned that
they're distributing it
to different countries
across Southeast Asia.
This is a major syndicate
with worldwide connections.
That's why we need to find out
who's behind it,
put a stop to their operations,
and hold them accountable
under the law.
And, uh, Head Agent Jacinto,
you'll be leading
this investigation.
It's time for you to step up.
- Sir, me?
- Yes.
I have great confidence in you,
which is why I'm entrusting
this major case to you.
You can do this.
We're right behind you, Ma'am.
I'll need all of your help.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DELGADO] This is your
first case as team leader.
How do you feel?
I'm ready to take on
the challenge, Sir.
Your father was a
former general in the NLEA.
I'm sure that's a heavy
responsibility to carry.
Honestly, Sir, I am nervous.
I don't even know
why you entrusted me
to lead the team.
Why would you doubt yourself?
The Zaragoza
Robbery Group case
and all the cases before that,
none of those criminals
would've been caught
without your skills.
Aside from being capable,
you have a good heart.
And if that's what guides you,
I'm sure you'll succeed.
Thank you very much, Sir.
Jacinto.
Don't doubt yourself.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hey, have some rice!
- Take some more.
[DANTE] I hope you've learned
your lesson, Gabo.
Be good from now on.
- Hey.
- What?
My nephew's always been
a good kid.
They're the ones
who keep picking on him.
Oh, that's true.
Gabo's not really
the troublemaker here.
They're the ones.
Especially Django's
and Mister Paquito's gang.
Exactly.
[BONG] That's true, Gabo.
Ever since you left,
Paquito and his gang...
...have been running
all the crime around here.
You know why?
Even the robbers,
snatchers, and scammers...
...are hiding out with us.
Why don't the cops arrest them?
How can they?
The cops are the ones
protecting them.
[RUDY] That's why you need
to be careful, Gabo.
It's dangerous
for outsiders here now.
Especially now that
Paquito's gang is growing.
Why should I be
careful around them, Pa?
Django's the reason
I ended up in prison.
I rotted in there
for eight years.
He better hide
when we cross paths.
[BETCHAY] Hey, Gabo.
Don't say that.
Stop getting
into fights already.
That's why
you keep getting hurt.
Straighten yourself out.
Learn your lesson.
Let's change the subject.
Wait a second.
Why didn't you
tell us you were coming?
- We would've picked you up.
- Exactly!
- What was that about?
- Right! Mh-mm.
Uh...
It all happened so suddenly, Pa.
I didn't expect
to get released so soon.
I was granted parole.
They granted you parole?
[MAMENG] That's great.
- [GABO] Uhm, auntie...
- [MAMENG] Hmm?
I really behaved
while I was in prison.
I did everything
they told me to do.
So even though I still had
a long sentence left,
they granted me parole
and released me early.
- Oh, wow.
- That's great.
- So that's how it works.
- That's nice.
- Just behave in prison.
- So that's possible.
Show me.
Here, sir.
[MAN] Sir! Sir!
So many illegal
connections here!
There's so much wiring here!
These people are unbelievable!
Always stealing electricity!
Go ahead. Cut them.
As long as they don't learn,
they'll never stop
using illegal connections.
Yes, sir. Let's go.
They won't stop
stealing electricity
- until those wires catch fire.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You hear me?
That's theft!
It's illegal!
[PEOPLE COMPLAINING]
If those wires catch fire,
all your houses
will burn down!
[PEOPLE COMPLAINING]
[FAN STOPS]
[HAIR CLIPPER BUZZING STOPS]
[POWER CUTS OFF]
- What happened?
- Power outage?
Go check
what's happening outside.
[MAN] You'll all burn!
Remember that!
It's illegal!
[PEOPLE COMPLAINING]
Remember that!
It's the Manelco.
Tell Mister Rudy what happened.
- This is exciting.
- [MAN] Yes! You never learn!
- Mister Rudy!
- Oh?
Our favorite visitors are here.
The Manelco is here.
They cutting us off again.
They've got some nerve.
How dare they cut off
our electricity
when we're paying so much!
- Hey! What now?!
- Oh no, there she is.
There she is! This is exciting.
Someone's losing it again!
You'll all burn!
You can't reconnect those!
[PEOPLE COMPLAINING]
Do you understand?
Listen to this guy!
Because you keep
doing it over and over!
Illegal connections!
What do you want?
You want us to pay?
You're charging way too much!
- That's right!
[BETCHAY] You keep adding
all kinds of charges!
It's so expensive!
Charges here, charges there!
And do you know why the
Philippines isn't progressing?
Because you keep robbing us
poor people!
- That's right!
What? You want us to play fair?
You're the ones
taking advantage of us!
You want us
to pay the right amount?
Then are your charges fair?
- That's right!
- Hey, Rudy.
Rudy, you know that's illegal.
You're stealing!
I can have you arrested!
- Hey!
[BETCHAY]
Who are you arresting?!
Go ahead. Try it!
[PEOPLE COMPLAINING]
Yes, what we're doing
may be wrong,
I'll have you all arrested!
but I hope those in power
also think about
what we're going through.
[OVERLAPPING VOICES COMPLAINING]
Even if they keep
cutting off our power,
they'll just tire
themselves out!
- That's right!
- Get lost!
- Tule!
Go climb it already!
- Tule! Tule! Tule!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
Neighbors!
The power's back!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
Hey! Hey!
What are we waiting for?
Neighbors! Let's celebrate!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
Unlimited power again!
Blast all your air conditioners!
Turn on every TV,
even if nobody's watching!
- Yes!
- Let's enjoy it!
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[WOMAN] Let's all buy
air conditioners!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- [PAQUITO] Django.
- Pa?
You're in charge here
while I'm gone.
Make sure
the business runs smoothly.
If anything comes up,
just give me a call.
Don't worry
about things here, Pa.
I'll handle everything.
Okay.
- Hmm.
- Oh?
Take care.
Take care, all of you.
[CHUCKLES WRYLY]
- They better be.
- [LAUGHS]
- Whatever.
- Oh...
- Where's my kiss?
- [SMOOCHES]
Oh, wow!
- Take care.
- Okay.
[HEAVY BEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- There!
- [TOLITS] Django!
- Django! Django! Django!
- Hurry up.
[DABOY] Django!
Hey!
You three! Where's your take?
[DABOY] Sorry, Django.
We couldn't pull anything off.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Ouch, Django!
You idiots!
Even the kids
have already hit their quota!
You haven't even
given me a single peso!
Things were really slow, Django.
We promise
we'll make up for it.
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Ouch!
- [THUD]
- [GRUNTS, GASPS]
Is that so?!
You useless losers!
Sorry, Django.
We promise we'll hit
our quota next time.
Sorry?
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS]
Wasn't our rule...
...that nobody comes back
to headquarters empty-handed?
- [SLAPS]
- [GRUNTS]
- Ouch!
- That hurts.
Why are you here?!
We were supposed
to tell you something,
but you kept slapping us.
How can we even say it?
- Oh, no!
- Don't get sarcastic with me!
- What is it?!
- It's important.
It's Gabo.
We saw him here.
He's out.
He went home.
G-Gabo?
Wasn't he supposed
to have years left?
How'd he get out?
We don't know.
[PEPE] Hey, Django, this is bad.
After all those years in prison,
he'll definitely come after you.
Django, let's call your father
and have him come back.
No.
Don't tell my father.
I'll deal with Gabo myself.
- Pulgas!
- Oh?
- Hurry up!
- Why?
Go find Gabo.
Tell him...
...to meet me
at the headquarters.
If he wants revenge,
we'll settle it here.
Tell him...
I'll make sure he's the one
they mourn
here in Ginintuang Lupa.
- Quick!
- Yes, boss! Come on!
Hurry up!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TEKLA] So, did you
miss it here, Gabo?
Miss Diday was fuming earlier.
And now, Manelco cut off
our electricity.
- Wow!
- [CHUCKLING]
It seems like we've given you
a warm welcome.
[BETCHAY] I think
it's the opposite.
Your arrival seems to be
a bad omen, isn't it?
[BETCHAY] I think before
you came here,
you should've gone someplace
else first to lose bad luck.
Look at this woman.
Aren't you happy
that Gabo's here?
[MAMENG] He has a chance
to start anew here.
Did I say I wasn't happy
about his return?
- I'm just saying that--
- No, what you're--
Wait a second!
My son has behaved now, okay?
He'll turn over a new leaf.
Won't you, son?
- Right?
- Really?
- Yes, Dad.
- See that?
- See?
- You didn't believe him.
I didn't say that
he wouldn't change!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Gabo!
- Aren't those Django's boys?
Hey, Gabo!
Django is asking for you.
What did he say?
If you're really brave,
you should face Django
at the stables.
That will let people know who's
the bigger man between you.
- Bigger man?
- Why is that needed?
Don't you agree to
his challenge, okay?
Get out of here!
- Go away!
- Get out of here!
You just got out of jail, Gabo.
You had just gotten freed!
Gabo, let me tell you this.
[BONG] Django will not stop
until he gets back at you.
[IPE] What can we say?
Django got humiliated
in their last fight.
He will never stop until
he takes revenge on you.
Gabo, don't listen to Ipe.
Besides, Gabo, you won't
be able to do anything
if you take on
Django's challenge.
You're already free. Don't let
yourself go back to jail.
[MAMENG] Or worse,
you could be killed.
[BETCHAY] What, Gabo?
Will you prove to us that
you have changed your ways now?
Gabo, you changed already,
haven't you?
Aren't you going to be nice now?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
That's great.
[BETCHAY SCOFFS] Really?
[RUDY] You have no trust in him.
[TEKLA] Do you really believe
that he's changed?
See?
You know, I'm delighted
to see Gabo like that.
He has really changed.
- [SCOFFS] Oh?
- You're delighted?
Aren't you wondering
if that's still Gabo?
That man's too different
from the Gabo we know.
Do you really think Gabo will
back down from Django?
- Think about it!
- [IPE] You saw it yourself.
He just left peacefully.
He wasn't looking for a fight.
He didn't bite back.
- That's right!
- The rumors are true.
I'm going to bet my life on it.
My son is turning
over a new leaf.
- [BONG] Okay.
- [IPE] I agree with you.
I'll make a bet against yours.
- Okay, call.
- Let's see.
- [DOOR CRASHES]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- Gabo!
- Let him face me!
- [SCREAMING CONTINUES]
- [POOL THUDS]
- Gabo! Stop!
- Where is he?!
- Huh? Where is he?!
- Gabo!
- Stop him!
Where is he?!
- What are we going to do?
- Get our stuff!
- This will be chaotic!
- Come on, hurry!
- Gabo!
- Where is he going?
Come on, we need to hurry!
We need to go!
- Where is Django hiding?
- We don't know!
- [BLADE SWISHES]
- Those are kids!
You're in danger now, Django!
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
Where's Django? Where is he?
[SHOUTING CONTINUES]
Where's Django?! Where is he?!
Django!
Come on, let's go!
Your Aunt Pinky has this piece
of property that we bought.
Where is it located?
In Ginintuang Lupa.
Aren't there a lot of
families there?
The people there are known
to be criminals too.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
This will be your end!
[MALE VO] Gabo and Django
will clash once again.
Gabo!
[MALE VO] The real gangster
will be revealed now.
You're the reason why
I was in jail for eight years!
You're going to pay for it all!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MALE VO] Coco Martin's Sigabo.